<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contributing on Aggregator</title><link>https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/</link><description>Recent content in Contributing on Aggregator</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction to Contributors</title><link>https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/developer-intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/developer-intro/</guid><description>So, you want to build yourself the binaries or want to fix a bug.
To enhance or fix bugs, please read Source code page to introduce yourself to the code. In Local build, we describe the build process: a mandatory read. Useful tips are contained in Debugging and Troubleshooting pages.
TFS Breaking changes # TFS Server API changed frequently in the past: TFS Aggregator contains specific checks for the TFS version.</description></item><item><title>Source Code</title><link>https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/source-code/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/source-code/</guid><description>This page explains the design and internal organization of TFS Aggregator v2&amp;rsquo;s code. If you want to rebuild, customize, submit changes this is the place to start.
Major Components # The Aggregator.Core assembly contains the logic to process a Work Item and run the aggregate scripts. It is normally used by Aggregator.ServerPlugin which intercept the TFS server side events and forward them to Aggregator.Core. Aggregator.ConsoleApp is a simple console app that helps users in developing and testing policies without installing the server plugin.</description></item><item><title>Local Build</title><link>https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/local-build/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/local-build/</guid><description>Building the Solution # To rebuild, edit or debug the code you must use Visual Studio 2017, Community or Professional Edition at a minimum. In addition you must install the following extensions from Visual Studio Gallery:
xUnit.net 1.0 WiX 3.10 (optional) TFS is not required to build nor debugging if you copy locally the required DLLs (for this latter you can use Remote Debugging). WiX is not required if you use the build-installer.</description></item><item><title>Debugging</title><link>https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/debugging/debugging/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/debugging/debugging/</guid><description>For the best development experience, use a TFS Virtual Machine with Visual Studio 2017 installed and work directly on the machine.
Do not ever debug on a production server!
Server Plugin # You can then set the output folder for the project to C:\Program Files\Microsoft Team Foundation Server 12.0\Application Tier\Web Services\bin\Plugins\ or use the deploy.cmd file in Aggregator.ServerPlugin project to refresh Aggregator&amp;rsquo;s assembly on a target test system.</description></item><item><title>Continuous Integration</title><link>https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/continuous-integration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/continuous-integration/</guid><description>We moved to VSTS for Continuous Integration.
CI Builds for:
develop feature/* do not produce artifacts, i.e. the MSI file. Builds that actually generate artifacts:
master release/* hotfix/* The Reference folder is filled with files from $/TfsAggregator2/References as the assemblies are not redistributable. As explained in Local build these assemblies are tied to the target TFS version.
The script build Debug and Release configuration of TFS-Aggregator-2.sln and run tests.</description></item><item><title>Documentation</title><link>https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/documentation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tfsaggregator.github.io/docs/v2/contrib/documentation/</guid><description>The source for documentation is tfsaggregator-docs-hugo. Note that you need to pull down also the theme submodule.
The master branch content must match the latest release. To prepare documentation for a future release, use a branch as in the code repository.
Get Hugo Hugo v0.18.1.
Run hugo server to test the changes locally.
Read the full details in this blog post.</description></item></channel></rss>